Can you finish on top?
After Porn Ends 3 is a documentary film directed by Brittany Andrews.
After Porn Ends 3 continues to explore whether a career as an adult performer is
inherently damaging to the balance of a perfomer's life once retired.
Self, played by Christy Canyon.
Self, played by Jenteal.
Self, played by Tera Patrick.
Self, played by Priya Rai.
Self, played by Bonnie Rotten.
Self, played by Jenna Presley.
After Porn Ends is a 2012 American documentary
film about the pornography industry.
It features interviews with Asia Carrera, Nina Hartley, Mary Carey, Randy West, Richard Pacheco, John
Leslie, Amber Lynn, Seka, Raylene, Bill Margold, Shelley Lubben, Luke Ford and Tiffany Million.
The film explores themes of porn star, sex talk, social
documentary, sex worker, informative.